creativematch.co.uk 2010-06-07

# creativematch | digital jobs, design jobs, new media jobs, marketing jobs, training, news, CV's & portfolios.

**Statement of intent  
**From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information(e.g. name and email address etc) in order to receive or use services on our website. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable creativematch to provide you with the services you select. Such information will treated in accordance with this policy.

Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive. Creativematch will act in accordance with UK legislation.

During the course of any visit to creativematch we may set a 'cookie'. Most websites do this, as cookies enable us to provide you with a better service (like making sure the content you see is the content you have selected) and it also assists us to analyse the profile of our visitors.

You can of course still visit the creativematch website with cookies disabled, but you may find some of the services are not available to you. 

**Storage and use of personal information**  
When you supply any personal information to creativematch we have legal obligations regarding the way we deal with that data. We must collect it fairly and we must explain how we will use it 

We do not make this information available to any third parties or 'companies in our group'

The only exception to this is if we are required to by Law. This also covers the content you publish on creativematch. If any content is offensive, abusive, disruptive or in any way illegal - creativematch reserve the right to omit the content and restrict your access to the website. In extreme circumstances and where required by Law, creativematch may pass on the personal details of any user uploading content which may prove to be illegal.

For safety and compliance with UK law, creativematch may store messaging transcript data

Where you have supplied a business or personal email address, creativematch may contact you with offers, news and functionality updates on the web site. We respect your privacy and as such do not provide this data for the express purpose of marketing to any third parties or companies 'in the group'. All emails sent by creativematch comply with industry best practice, and you can of course unsubscribe using links in the email.

**Access to your personal information**  
You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. You can manage your own content using our content management systems, these enable you to correct any inaccuracies or delete information - 24hrs a day. However, if you wish to see a hard copy, you can request this by contacting the IT Director, Creativematch, Building 3, Chiswick Park, 566 Chiswick High Road, London W4 5YA. Please send your request and include a cheque for £11.75 made payable to creativematch.

**Age restriction**  
If you are under 16, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to us. Please do not provide us with personal information if you are under 16 years old.
